(this.webpackJsonptechquiz=this.webpackJsonptechquiz||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,n){},14:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t),n.d(t,"TechQuiz",(function(){return f}));var s=n(2),o=n(3),a=n(7),i=n(5),r=n(0),c=n.n(r),u=n(4),l=n.n(u),h=(n(13),[{question:"______ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript?",answers:["Microsoft","Navigator","LiveWire","Native"],correct:"Navigator",questionId:"099099"},{question:"__________ JavaScript is also called server-side JavaScript?",answers:["Microsoft","Navigator","LiveWire","Native"],correct:"LiveWire",questionId:"183452"},{question:"Which of the following attribute can hold the JavaScript version??",answers:["Language","Script","Version","None of the above"],correct:"Language",questionId:"267908"},{question:"Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",answers:["<js>","<scripting>","<script>","<javascript>"],correct:"<script>",questionId:"333247"},{question:"The _______ method of an Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array?",answers:["Reverse","Shift","Slice","Splice"],correct:"Splice",questionId:"496293"},{question:"Which built-in method returns the length of the string?",answers:["length()","size()","index()","None of the above"],correct:"length()",questionId:"298060"},{question:"How are the objects organized in the HTML DOM?",answers:["list","stack","queue","Hierarchy"],correct:"Hierarchy",questionId:"3096579"},{question:"What among the following is an appropriate when an event occurs when the user clicks on an element?",answers:["onclick","onchange","onkeyup","onblur"],correct:"onclick",questionId:"3182461"},{question:"What among the following is an appropriate event handler for input text among the below options ?",answers:["onclick","onchange","onkeyup","onblur"],correct:"onchange",questionId:"3239112"},{question:"What is the default value of the asyc attribute?",answers:["0","1","False","True"],correct:"True",questionId:"3318503"},{question:"Which tag(s) can handle mouse events in Netscape?",answers:["<img>","<a>","<br>","<span>"],correct:"<img>",questionId:"3410327"},{question:"Which of the following method checks if its argument is not a number?",answers:["isNaN()","nonNaN()","NaN()","None of the above"],correct:"isNaN",questionId:"3542596"},{question:"What are the two basic groups of dataypes in JavaScript?",answers:["Primitive","Reference types","All of the above","None of the above"],correct:"All of the above",questionId:"3667517"},{question:"What are the types of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?",answers:["Alert","Prompt","Confirm","All of the above"],correct:"All of the above",questionId:"3791672"},{question:" Which of them is not the looping structures in JavaScript?",answers:["for","while","fotwhich"," dowhile"],correct:"while",questionId:"3893585"},{question:"Among the keywords below, which one is not a statement?",answers:["if","with","debugger","use strict"],correct:"use strict",questionId:"3913430"},{question:"mong the following, which one is a ternary operator in JavaScript?",answers:["#",": :","& :","? :"],correct:"? :",questionId:"4049121"},{question:"What is the original name of JavaScript?",answers:["LiveScript","EScript","Mocha","JavaScript"],correct:"Mocha",questionId:"4150746"},{question:"Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",answers:["<script>","<head>","<meta>","<style>"],correct:"<script>",questionId:"4235063"},{question:"Which company developed JavaScript?",answers:["Netscape","Bell Labs","Sun Microsystems","IBM"],correct:"Netscape",questionId:"4321002"},{question:" Which of the following is not JavaScript Data Types?",answers:["Undefined","Number","Boolean","Float"],correct:"Float",questionId:"4442286"},{question:"We can embed JS code inside HTML directly ?",answers:["True","False"],correct:"True",questionId:"4564430"},{question:"Local Browser used for validations on the Web Pages uses __________?",answers:["CSS","JS","HTML","Java"],correct:"JS",questionId:"4630606"},{question:"JavaScript Code is written inside file having extension __________?",answers:[".javascript",".jsc",".js",".jvs"],correct:".js",questionId:"4795960"},{question:"Which candy is NOT made by Mars?",answers:["Compiled","Interpreted","Complicated","Integrated"],correct:"Interpreted",questionId:"4811162"},{question:"Javascript is _________ language?",answers:["Scripting","None of These","Application","Programming"],correct:"Scripting",questionId:"4982981"},{question:"Which of the following function of String object returns the character at the specified index?",answers:["charAt()","charCodeAt()","concat()","indexOf()"],correct:"charAt()",questionId:"4982981"},{question:"Javascript is _________ language?",answers:["Scripting","None of These","Application","Programming"],correct:"Scripting",questionId:"4982981"}]),p=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(h.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},d=n(6),v=function(e){var t=e.question,n=e.options,s=e.selected,o=Object(r.useState)(n),a=Object(d.a)(o,2),i=a[0],u=a[1];return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},t),i.map((function(e,t){return c.a.createElement("button",{key:t,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){u([e]),s(e)}},e)})))},q=function(e){var t=e.score,n=e.playAgain;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},"You scored ",t," / 5 correct answers!"),c.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:n},"Play again!"))},f=function(e){Object(a.a)(n,e);var t=Object(i.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(s.a)(this,n);for(var o=arguments.length,a=new Array(o),i=0;i<o;i++)a[i]=arguments[i];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(a))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){p().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(t,n){t===n&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(o.a)(n,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"},"TechQuiz"),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(t){var n=t.question,s=t.answers,o=t.correct,a=t.questionID;return c.a.createElement(v,{question:n,options:s,key:a,selected:function(t){return e.computeAnswer(t,o)}})})),5===this.state.responses?c.a.createElement(q,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null)}}]),n}(r.Component);l.a.render(c.a.createElement(f,null),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.40f35078.chunk.js.map